Guide to the Montana State University Extension Service Records 1912-1970
Montana State University Library, Archives and Special Collections, Manuscript Collections
- Indian Reservation Agents Annual Reports, 1955-1970; 2
  - Blackfeet Reservation; Robert E. Durham, Bonita J. Olney, 1956-1957 (Box 70, Folder 8-9)
  - Blackfeet Reservation; Bob Durham, Assoc. Agent, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Blackfeet Reservation; Robert E. Durham, Assoc. Agent, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Blackfeet Reservation; Robert Durham, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Blackfeet Reservation; Robert E. Durham, Dorothy Gallup, 1961-1964 (Box 70, Folder 13-16)
  - Blackfeet Reservation; Robert E. Durham, Marilyn Cole, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Blackfeet Reservation; Marilyn Cole, Robert Durham, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  - Blackfeet Reservation, 1967-1970 (Box 70, Folder 19-22)
  - Program of Work, Crow Reservation; N. A. Jacobsen, Clementine Sittel, 1950 (Box 70, Folder 23)
  - Crow Reservation; Howard J. Morton, Associate C.A., 1958 (Box 70, Folder 24)
  - Crow Reservation; Howard Morton, Associate Agent, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 25)
  - Crow Reservation; Howard J. Morton, Ada L. King, 1960-1966 (Box 70, Folder 26-32)
  - Crow Reservation, 1967-1970 (Box 70, Folder 33-36)
  - Long Time Program, Crow Reservation, 1969-1974 (Box 70, Folder 37)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation; John P. Biggle, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 38)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation; W. Doyle Stocks, John Biggle, Associate C.A.s, 1958 (Box 70, Folder 39)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation; W. Doyle Stocks, Associate Agent, 1959 (Box 70, Folder 40)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation; W. Doyle Stokes, Olaf J. Brekke, 1960 (Box 70, Folder 41)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation; Olaf J. Brekke, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 42)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation; Olaf J. Brekke, 1962 (Box 70, Folder 43)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation; Olaf J. Brekke, Louisa Starkey, 1963 (Box 70, Folder 44)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation; Olaf Brekke, Louisa Starkey, 1964 (Box 70, Folder 45)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation; Olaf J. Brekke, Grace Miller, 1965 (Box 70, Folder 46)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation; Olaf Brekke, Grace Miller, 1966 (Box 70, Folder 47)
  - Fort Belknap Reservation, 1967-1970 (Box 70, Folder 48-51)
  - Long Time Program, Fort Belknap Reservation, 1969-1974 (Box 70, Folder 52)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Elisabeth Hart, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 70, Folder 53)
  - Fort Peck Reservation, 1932-1936 (Box 70, Folder 54-58)
  - Fort Peck Reservation, 1937 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Hannes Hallgrimson, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Leo F. Kleffner, Maud R. Sharer, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Hannes A. Hallgrimson, Marie Roeseler, Don L. Hunter, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Alfred G. Thorson, Maud R. Sharer, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Hannes A, Hallgrimson, Marie R. Hendricks, Don L. Hunter, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Alfred G. Thornson, Maud R. Sharer, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Robert Weber, Associate Agent, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Maud Sharer, Associate H.D.A., Alfred Thorson, Associate Agent, 1958 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Bob Weber, Rupert Nelson, Assoc. Agents; Joyce Wheeler, Assoc. H.D.A., 1959 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Maud R. Sharer, Assoc. H.D.A.; Al Thorson, Assoc. Agent, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Rupert Nelson, Joyce W. Simpson, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Maud Sharer, Amarlys Weinmeister, A. Thornson, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Rupert Nelson, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Amarlys Weinmeister, B. M. Nagle, Alfred G. Thornson, James M. Quanbeck, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Rupert R. Nelson, Patricia R. Paugh, Don L. Hunter, Emery Anderson, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; James M. Quanbeck, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 16)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Henry Botch, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Gene Thompson, Dorothy Hofman, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Henry Botch, 1964 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Henry K. Botch, 1965 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  - Fort Peck Reservation; Henry Botch, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  - Fort Peck Reservation, 1968 December 1-1969 June 30 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  - Fort Peck Reservation, 1969-1970 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  - Northern Cheyenne Reservation; William J. Cutler, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  - Northern Cheyenne Reservation; C. Eugene Phillips, Associate C.A., 1958 (Box 71, Folder 25)
  - Northern Cheyenne Reservation; C. Eugene Phillips, Robert Weber, Assoc. Agents, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  - Northern Cheyenne Reservation; Robert A. Weber, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  - Northern Cheyenne Reservation; Robert Weber, Hazel A. Thompson, 1961-1966 (Box 71, Folder 28-33)
  - Northern Cheyenne Reservation, 1967-1970 (Box 71, Folder 34-37)
  - Long Time Program, Northern Cheyenne Reservation, 1969-1974 (Box 71, Folder 38)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; Robert A. Roush, 1955 (Box 71, Folder 39)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; Robert F. Bucher, Robert A. Roush, 1956 (Box 71, Folder 40)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; R. F. Bucher, R. A. Roush, Ruth M. Poetter, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; Robert F. Bucher, C.A.; Robert Roush, Assoc. Agent; Ruth Mae Poetter, H.D.A., 1958 (Box 71, Folder 42)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; Robert A. Roush, Myrtle Bosch, Assistant Agents, 1959 (Box 71, Folder 43)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; Robert A. Roush, Myrtle F. Bosch, 1960 (Box 71, Folder 44)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; Robert A. Roush, Avis A. Stapleton, Myrtle F. Bosch, 1961 (Box 71, Folder 45)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; Robert A. Roush, Avis A. Stapleton, 1962 (Box 71, Folder 46)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; Robert Roush, Avis Stapleton, 1963 (Box 71, Folder 47)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; Robert A. Roush, Elinor R. Clack, 1964-1965 (Box 71, Folder 48-49)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation; Robert Roush, Elinor Clack, 1966 (Box 71, Folder 50)
  - Rocky Boy Reservation, 1967-1970 (Box 71, Folder 51-54)
  - Long Time Program, Rocky Boy Reservation, 1969-1974 (Box 71, Folder 55)
- Special Projects Annual Reports, 1926-1953; 3
  Several individual agricultural communities were assigned their own agents in addition to the county agents. The Huntley, Milk River, Sun River and Western Montana irrigation projects had their own agents who also filed annual reports. The folders in this series have been arranged alphabetically by project name, and then chronologically within that project name sort.
  - Huntley Irrigation Project; M. M. Oliphant, Assoc. Agent, 1926 (Box 71, Folder 56)
  - Huntley Irrigation Project; G. A. Rassley, Assoc. Agent, 1927 (Box 71, Folder 57)
  - Huntley Irrigation Project; G. A. Rassley, Assoc. Agent, 1928 (Box 71, Folder 58)
  - Huntley Irrigation Project; T. B. Holker, Assoc. Agent, 1929 (Box 71, Folder 59)
  - Huntley Irrigation Project; T. B. Holker, Assoc. Agent, 1930 (Box 71, Folder 60)
  - Huntley Irrigation Project; K. P. Jones, Assoc. Agent, 1931 (Box 71, Folder 61)
  - Huntley Irrigation Project; K. Jones, Assoc. Agent, 1932-1933 (Box 71, Folder 62-63)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; G. H. Bingham, Assoc. Agent, 1929-1930 (Box 71, Folder 64-65)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; G. H. Bingham, Assoc. Agent, 1931-1934 (Box 72, Folder 1-4)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project, 1935 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; I. D. Zobell, 1936 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; I. D. Zobell, Glenn Baird, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; Glenn Baird, 1938 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; Donald J. Luebbe, Assoc. Agent, 1941 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; Don Luebbe, 1942 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; Donald J. Luebbe, G. H. Bingham, Assoc. Agents, 1943 (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; Reed W. Magleby, Assoc. Agent, 1944 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; Parker E. Heikes, 1949-1951 (Box 72, Folder 13-15)
  - Milk River Irrigation Project; Parker Eugene Heikes, 1952 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; D. P. Thurber, Assoc. Agent, 1929-1931 (Box 72, Folder 17-19)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; D. P. Thurber, Assoc. Extension Agent, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; D. P. Thurber, Assoc. Agent, 1933 (Box 72, Folder 21)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; D. P. Thurber, Assoc. Agent, 1934 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Claude C. Windecker, Assistant Agent, 1935 (Box 72, Folder 23)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Claude Windecker, 1936 (Box 72, Folder 24)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Claude Windecker, Assoc. Agent, 1937 (Box 72, Folder 25)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Claude Windecker, 1938 (Box 72, Folder 26)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Glenn Baird, 1939 (Box 72, Folder 27)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Glenn Baird, Assoc. Agent, 1940 (Box 72, Folder 28)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Glenn Baird, Assoc. Agent, 1941 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Glenn Baird, 1942 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Glenn Baird, Assoc. Agent, 1943 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Joe W. Eisenman, Assoc. Agent, 1944 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Joe Eisenman, Assoc. Agent, 1945 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Stanley W. Howard, Assoc. Agent, 1947 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Sun River Irrigation Project; Stanley Howard, 1948 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Western Montana Project; Stanley Howard, 1950-1951 (Box 73, Folder 8-9)
  - Western Montana Project; Darrell Fenner, 1952 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Western Montana Project; Darrell E. Fenner, 1953 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Specialist Annual Reports, 1917-1968; 4
  - Agent-at-Large; F. G. Fuller, 1918 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Agent-at-Large; Frances Bellamy, H.D.A., 1930 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Agent-at-Large; Frances Bellamy, H.D.A., 1931 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Agent-at-Large; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1934 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Agent-at-Large; Eleanor Harrer, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Agent-at-Large; Florence Michaelson, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Agent-at-Large; Hazel Thompson, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Agent-at-Large; Lillian Tubb, H.D.A., 1935 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Agent-at-Large; Helen Allen, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Agent-at-Large; Margaret Conlon, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Agent-at-Large; Eleanor Harrer, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Agent-at-Large; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 73, Folder 23)
  - Agent-at-Large; Hazel Thompson, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 73, Folder 24)
  - Agent-at-Large; Lillian Tubb, H.D.A., 1936 (Box 73, Folder 25)
  - Agent-at-Large; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 73, Folder 26)
  - Agent-at-Large; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 73, Folder 27)
  - Agent-at-Large; Hazel Thompson, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 73, Folder 28)
  - Agent-at-Large; Edith Watson, H.D.A., 1937 (Box 73, Folder 29)
  - Agent-at-Large; Margaret B. Conlon, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 73, Folder 30)
  - Agent-at-Large; Lois Knowlton, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 73, Folder 31)
  - Agent-at-Large; Lillian Stone, H.D.A., 1938 (Box 73, Folder 32)
  - 44 H.D.A. Agents-at-Large; Big Horn, Blaine, Chouteau, Custer, Fergus, 1935-1944 (Box 73, Folder 33)
  - Agent-at-Large; Alma R. Ragar, H.D.A., 1947 (Box 73, Folder 34)
  - Agent-at-Large; Manuel Atwood, 1948 (Box 73, Folder 35)
  - Agent-at-Large; Wm. P. Thomas, 1949 (Box 73, Folder 36)
  - Agent-at-Large; W. P. Thomas, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 37)
  - Agronomy; A. J. Ogaard, 1926-1927 (Box 73, Folder 38-39)
  - Agronomy; L. D. Kurtz, 1928 (Box 73, Folder 40)
  - Agronomy; L. D. Kurtz, Waldo Kidder, 1929 (Box 73, Folder 41)
  - Agronomy; Waldo Kidder, 1930-1931 (Box 73, Folder 42-44)
  - Agronomy; Sam L. Sloan, 1932-1935 (Box 73, Folder 45-48)
  - Agronomy; Ralph D. Mercer, 1936-1944 (Box 73, Folder 49-57)
  - Agronomy; Ralph D. Mercer, 1945-1952 (Box 74, Folder 1-8)
  - Agronomy; Arthur F. Shaw, Ralph D. Mercer, 1953-1955 (Box 74, Folder 9-11)
  - Agronomy; Ralph D. Mercer, Arthur F. Shaw, 1956-1959 (Box 74, Folder 12-15)
  - Agronomy; Ralph Mercer, Arthur Shaw, 1960 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Agronomy; Arthur F. Shaw, Ralph D. Mercer, 1961 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Agronomy; Arthur F. Shaw, 1962-1963 (Box 74, Folder 18-19)
  - Agronomy; Arthur F. Shaw, 1964-1966 (Box 75, Folder 1-3)
  - Agronomy; Mike Jackson, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Agronomy; Arthur Shaw, 1967 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Agronomy; M. J. Jackson, Specialist, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Agronomy; Arthur F. Shaw, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Brucellosis Control; Howard Welch, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Childhood Development; Josephine Pollock, 1933 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Child Development and Parent Education; Josephine Pollock, 1934 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Child Development; Josephine Pollock, 1935-1937 (Box 75, Folder 11-13)
  - Clothing; Ruth Patchin, 1921 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Clothing; Ruth Patchin, Inez LaBossier, 1921-1922 (Box 75, Folder 15-16)
  - Clothing; Inez LaBossier, 1923-1925 (Box 75, Folder 17-19)
  - Clothing; Inez LaBossier, Edith J. Mott, 1926 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Clothing; Edith J. Mott, 1927-1928 (Box 75, Folder 21-22)
  - Clothing; Edith J. Mott, Hazel Kidder, 1929 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Clothing; Hazel Kidder, 1930 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Clothing; Hazel Kidder Porter, 1931 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Clothing; Hazel Kidder, Josephine Pollock, 1932 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Clothing; Josephine Pollock, 1933-1936 (Box 75, Folder 27-30)
  - Clothing; Josephine Pollock, Mary Omen, 1937 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Clothing; Martha L. Hensley, 1938-1945 (Box 75, Folder 32-39)
  - Clothing; Lora V. Hilyard, 1946-1962 (Box 76, Folder 1-18)
  - Clothing; Harriet Doan, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Dairy, 1915 (Box 76, Folder 20-21)
  - Dairy; W. E. Tomson, 1919-1920 (Box 76, Folder 22-23)
  - Dairy; J. O. Tretsven, 1922-1930 (Box 76, Folder 24-31)
  - Dairy; G. C. Sands, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Dairy; J. O. Tretsven, J. A. Nelson, G. C. Sands, 1933 (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Dairy; J. O. Tretsven, J. A. Nelson, 1934-1936 (Box 76, Folder 34-39)
  - Dairy; J. O. Tretsven, 1937 (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - Dairy; J. O. Tretsven, J. A. Nelson, 1938-1939 (Box 76, Folder 38-39)
  - Dairy; J. O. Tretsven, 1940 (Box 76, Folder 40)
  - Dairy; J. O. Tretsven, J. A. Nelson, 1941-1943 (Box 76, Folder 41-43)
  - Dairy; J. O. Tretsven, 1944 (Box 76, Folder 44)
  - Dairy; J. O. Tretsven, J. A. Nelson, 1945 (Box 76, Folder 45)
  - Dairy and Swine; J. O. Tretsven, J. A. Nelson, 1946 (Box 76, Folder 46)
  - Dairy and Swine; J. O. Tretsven, 1947 (Box 76, Folder 47)
  - Dairy; J. O. Tretsven, 1948 (Box 76, Folder 48)
  - Dairy and Swine; J. O. Tretsven, 1949-1955 (Box 76, Folder 49-55)
  - Dairy and Swine; J. O. Tretsven, A. O. Jacobs, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 56)
  - Dairy; A. O. Jacobs, 1957 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Dairy and Swine; A. O. Jacobs, 1958 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Dairy; Arthor Jacobs, Earl J. Peace, 1959 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Dairy and Swine; Earl J. Peace, 1960-1968 (Box 77, Folder 4-12)
  - Economics; Paul Carpenter, 1933 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Economics; H. G. Bolster, 1935-1936 (Box 77, Folder 14-15)
  - Economics; Willard Lamphere, 1936 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Economics; H. G. Bolster, 1937 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Economics; Willard Lamphere, 1937 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - "Some Aspects of Agricultural Planning in Montana", Economics; H. G. Bolster, 1938 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Economics; H. G. Bolster, 1938 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Economics; Willard Lamphere, 1938-1939 (Box 77, Folder 21-22)
  - Economics; H. G. Bolster, 1940-1945 (Box 77, Folder 23-26)
  - Economics; H. R. Stucky, 1946 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Economics; H. R. Stucky, 1947 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Economics; Ralph Stucky, 1949 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Economics; H. R. Stucky, 1950-1953 (Box 77, Folder 30-33)
  - Economics; H. R. Stucky, M. E. Quenemon, 1954 (Box 77, Folder 34)
  - Economics; John C. Bower, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 35)
  - Economics; John C. Bower, 1956-1960 (Box 78, Folder 1-5)
  - Economics; M. E. Quenemon, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Economics; S. J. Tietema, 1962 (Box 78, Folder 7-8)
  - Economics; M. E. Quenemon, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Economics; S. J. Tietema, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Economics; M. E. Quenemon, S. J. Tietema, 1964-1965 (Box 78, Folder 11-12)
  - Economics; S. Tietema, R. Bucher, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Economics; John Bower, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Economics; Luft, Bucher, Tietema, 1967 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Economics; "Agricultural outlook and Public Affairs", John C. Bower, 1968 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Emergency Programs; A. W. Ayers, Emergency Agent, 1933 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Emergency Programs; Albert J. Borton, State Compliance Agent, 1934 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - State Livestock Purchase Program, Emergency Programs; Paul Carpenter, Willard Lamphere, 1934 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Emergency Programs; Report of the Sugar Beet Production Adjustment, G. H. Bingham, 1935 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Farm Labor, Emergency Programs, 1943-1947 (Box 78, Folder 21-24)
  - Farm Labor Program, Emergency Programs, 1947 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - (Ag.) Engineering; E. B. Wilson, 1946-1960 (Box 78, Folder 26-39)
  - Entomology; F. E. Price, 1922 (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - Entomology; W. Bruce Mabee, 1926 (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - Entomology; W. B. Mabee, 1927-1930 (Box 78, Folder 42-45)
  - Entomology; J. H. Pepper, 1950-1960 (Box 78, Folder 46-56)
  - Entomology; Ray Pratt, 1963 (Box 78, Folder 57)
  - Entomology; M. J. Jackson, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 58)
  - Entomology; Ray Pratt, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 59)
  - Family Life; Amy E. Wold, 1949-1962 (Box 78, Folder 60-78)
  - Farm Management; M. L. Wilson, 1923 (Box 78, Folder 79)
  - Farm Management; B. F. Alvord, 1927-1928 (Box 78, Folder 80-81)
  - Farm Management; V. D. Gilman, 1929-1931 (Box 78, Folder 82-83)
  - Farm Management; C. H. Peterson, 1932-1933 (Box 78, Folder 84-85)
  - Farm Management; Austin Goth, 1934 (Box 78, Folder 86-87)
  - Farm Management; Austin Goth, Clyde Howard, 1935 (Box 78, Folder 88-89)
  - Farm Management; Clyde Howard, 1936 (Box 78, Folder 90-91)
  - Farm Management; Clyde Howard, 1937 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Farm Management; John C. Bower, 1938-1941 (Box 79, Folder 2-6)
  - Farm Management; M. E. Quenemoen, 1955-1956 (Box 79, Folder 7-8)
  - Farm Management; M. E. Quenemoen, Warren L. Trock, 1957-1960 (Box 79, Folder 9-12)
  - Farm Management; Quenemoen, M. E., Bucher, R. F., Luft, Leroy D., 1968 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Fish and Wildlife; Eldon H. Smith, 1955-1967 (Box 79, Folder 14-22)
  - Food and Nutrition; Mary Ann Graber, 1921 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Food and Nutrition; Mary Ann Graber, Martha Mae Hunter, 1922 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Food and Nutrition; Martha Mae Thompson, Susanne Thompson, 1924 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Food and Nutrition; Susanne Thompson, 1925 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Food and Nutrition; Susanne Thompson, Jessie McQueen, 1926 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Food and Nutrition; Jessie McQueen, 1927-1928 (Box 79, Folder 28-29)
  - Food and Nutrition; Jessie McQueen, Frances Smith, 1929 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Food and Nutrition; Frances Smith, 1930 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Supplement to, Food and Nutrition, 1930 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Food and Nutrition; Frances Smith, 1931-1935 (Box 79, Folder 33-37)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Frances Smith, Bessie E. McClelland, 1936 (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Bessie E. McClelland, 1937-1940 (Box 80, Folder 1-4)
  - Montana State Nutrition Committee Report, 1940-1945 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Bessie E. McClelland, 1941-1946 (Box 80, Folder 6-11)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1947 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Miss Mary E. Loughead, 1948 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Marketing Information, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1950 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1950 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Marketing Information, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Marketing Information, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Marketing Information, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Marketing Information, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Marketing Information, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1955-1957 (Box 80, Folder 26-28)
  - Marketing Information, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1958 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1958 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Marketing Information, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1959 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Marketing Information, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1960 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Marketing Information, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Plan of Work, Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - Foods and Nutrition; Mary E. Loughead, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 37-38)
  - Forestry; Richard T. Marks, 1957-1964 (Box 80, Folder 39-46)
  - 4-H, 1917 (Box 80, Folder 47)
  - 4-H; Chas. E. Potter, 1919-1922 (Box 80, Folder 48-51)
  - 4-H; Emily Linhoff, District Club Leader, 1923 (Box 80, Folder 52)
  - 4-H; Chas. E. Potter, 1923-1924 (Box 80, Folder 53-54)
  - 4-H, 1925 (Box 80, Folder 55)
  - 4-H; Chas. E. Potter, 1926-1927 (Box 80, Folder 56-57)
  - 4-H, 1928-1938 (Box 80, Folder 58-68)
  - 4-H, 1939-1947 (Box 81, Folder 1-9)
  - 4-H; T. W. Thompson, Geraldine Fenn, Margaret Kohl, Dana O. Schrupp, 1949 (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - 4-H; Paul Moore, Geraldine Fenn, Margaret Kohl, Janice Fenske, 1950 (Box 81, Folder 11)
  - 4-H; Paul Moore, Geraldine Fenn, Margaret Kohl, 1951-1952 (Box 81, Folder 12-13)
  - 4-H; Paul Moore, Geraldine Fenn, Esther Rugland, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - 4-H; Miss Fenn, Miss Rugland, Mr. Paul J. Moore, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - 4-H; Paul J. Moore, Geraldine G. Fenn, Esther R. Rugland, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 16)
  - 4-H; Paul J. Moore, Geraldine G. Fenn, C. W. Vaughn, Esther R. Brekke, 1956 (Box 81, Folder 17)
  - 4-H; Paul J. Moore, Geraldine G. Fenn, Esther R. Brekke, C. W. Vaughn, 1957 (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - 4-H; Paul Moore, Geraldine Fenn, C. W. Vaughn, Margaret Kohl, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 19)
  - 4-H; Paul J. Moore, C. W. Vaughn, Geraldine G. Fenn, Margaret A. Kohl, 1959-1960 (Box 81, Folder 20-21)
  - 4-H; M. J. Stangl, Home Ec. Specialist, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 22)
  - 4-H; M. J. Stangl, Home Ec. Specialist, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 23)
  - Health; Frances McDonald, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Field Reports, Health; Frances McDonald, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Health; Frances Hixon McDonald, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Field Reports, Health; Frances McDonald, 1947 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Health; Frances Hixon McDonald, 1948-1956 (Box 82, Folder 5-13)
  - Home Economics; Katherine Jensen, 1915 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Home Economics; Bessie E. McClelland, Martha Dunlap, Louise Shunk, 1959 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Home Economics; Bess McClelland, Louise Shunk, Martha Dunlap, Mae F. True, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 16)